// Quiz Questions
export const questions = [
{
    id: "1",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question: "What House Does Harry Potter Belong To?",
    answer_A: "Hufflepuff",
    answer_B: "Gryffindor",
    answer_C: "Slytherin",
    answer_D: "Ravenclaw",
    correct_answer: "B",
},
{
    id: "2",
    medium: "Medium",
    question: "What is Mr. Filchʻs Job at Hogwarts?",
    answer_A: "Janitor",
    answer_B: "Engineer",
    answer_C: "Housekeeper",
    answer_D: "Caretaker",
    correct_answer: "D",
},
{
    id: "3",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question: "How are students put into their houses?",
    answer_A: "A Structured Quiz",
    answer_B: "A Choosing Spell",
    answer_C: "They receive a letter",
    answer_D: "The Sorting Hat",
    correct_answer: "D",
},
{
    id: "4",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question: "What is Voldemortʻs full birth name?",
    answer_A: "Tom Marvolo Riddle",
    answer_B: "Tom Sectumsempra Riddle",
    answer_C: "Tom Riddle",
    answer_D: "Tom Lord Riddle",
    correct_answer: "A",
},
{
    id: "5",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question: "Which word does NOT describe a wizard/witch with muggle parents?",
    answer_A: "Dirty-blood",
    answer_B: "Muggle-Born",
    answer_C: "Mudblood",
    answer_D: "Bleeder",
    correct_answer: "D",
},
{
    id: "6",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question: "What Does The Marauderʻs Map Show?",
    answer_A: "Every protective spell around Hogwarts",
    answer_B: "The location of everyone at Hogwarts",
    answer_C: "A Map to the Marauderʻs Treasure",
    answer_D: "How to get past the Whomping Willow",
    correct_answer: "B",
},
{
    id: "7",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question: "Which of the following people is NOT an animagus?",
    answer_A: "Remus Lupin",
    answer_B: "Victor Crum",
    answer_C: "Sirius Black",
    answer_D: "Proffesor McGonagall",
    correct_answer: "A",
},
{
    id: "8",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question: "Why was the Whomping Willow planted?",
    answer_A: "To pay tribute to past heroes of the school",
    answer_B: "To protect Remus Lupin",
    answer_C: "To protect Sirius Black",
    answer_D: "To train students in Defense against the Dark Arts",
    correct_answer: "B",
},
{
    id: "9",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question: "What is the name of Malfoyʻs Mother?",
    answer_A: "Bellatrix",
    answer_B: "Nagini",
    answer_C: "Narcissa",
    answer_D: "Magenta",
    correct_answer: "C",
},
{
    id: "10",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    question: "Who betrayed The Order while Harry was being rescued from the Dursleyʻs house?",
    answer_A: "Alastor Moody",
    answer_B: "Mundungus Fletcher",
    answer_C: "Kingsley",
    answer_D: "None Of The Above. There was no traitor.",
    correct_answer: "B",
},
{
    id: "11",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question: "What does R.A.B. stand for?",
    answer_A: "Regulus Argulus Black",
    answer_B: "Regulus Arcturus Black",
    answer_C: "Ridikulus Acheiving Barter",
    answer_D: "Regulus Artemus Black",
    correct_answer: "B",
},
{
    id: "12",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question: "Who is Fluffly?",
    answer_A: "Hagridʻs Spider",
    answer_B: "Lockhartʻs Pet",
    answer_C: "Hagridʻs Dog",
    answer_D: "The Dog defending the sorcererʻs stone",
    correct_answer: "C",
},
{
    id: "13",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question: "What does the Imperius Curse Do?",
    answer_A: "Kills the targeted person",
    answer_B: "Severly sickens the targted person",
    answer_C: "Tortures the targeted person",
    answer_D: "Controls the targeted person",
    correct_answer: "D",
},
{
    id: "14",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question: "The TIme Turner allows the user travel back in time at multiples of ____ minutes?",
    answer_A: "30",
    answer_B: "60",
    answer_C: "90",
    answer_D: "120",
    correct_answer: "B",
},
{
    id: "15",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question: "What is the name of Voldermortʻs followers?",
    answer_A: "The Death Eaters",
    answer_B: "Voldemortʻs Army",
    answer_C: "The Salazar Wizards",
    answer_D: "The Dark Wizards",
    correct_answer: "A",
},
{
    id: "16",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question: "Which of the following wizards was not a death Eater during the first wizarding war?",
    answer_A: "Vincent Crabbe",
    answer_B: "Lucius Malfoy",
    answer_C: "Severus Snape",
    answer_D: "Gregory Goyle",
    correct_answer: "C",
},
{
    id: "17",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question: "Which of the following spells will slow down a target?",
    answer_A: "Reducto",
    answer_B: "Impedimenta",
    answer_C: "Flipendo",
    answer_D: "Immobulus",
    correct_answer: "B",
},
{
    id: "18",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question: "What is the function of the spell, ʻFinite Incantatumʻ?",
    answer_A: "To strengthen your previous spell",
    answer_B: "To confuse your target surrounding then with a shroud",
    answer_C: "To Knock your enemy off balance",
    answer_D: "To stop any spell",
    correct_answer: "D",
},
{
    id: "20",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question: "What is the first spell Harry Potter learned at Hogwarts according to the movie?",
    answer_A: "Oculus Reparo",
    answer_B: "Wingardium Leviosa",
    answer_C: "Stupefy",
    answer_D: "Alohamora",
    correct_answer: "B",
},
{
    id: "21",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question: "What animal can Professor McGonagall turn into?",
    answer_A: "Cat",
    answer_B: "Dog",
    answer_C: "Leopard",
    answer_D: "Pixy",
    correct_answer: "A",
},
{
    id: "22",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question: "Who disguises themself as Mad-Eye Moody in the fourth book/movie?",
    answer_A: "Peter Pettigrew",
    answer_B: "Voldemort",
    answer_C: "Barty Crouch Jr.",
    answer_D: "Hatcher Fleming",
    correct_answer: "C",
},
{
    id: "23",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    question: "Which of the following characters became a professional Quidditch palyer?",
    answer_A: "Ginny",
    answer_B: "Ron",
    answer_C: "Hermione",
    answer_D: "Harry",
    correct_answer: "A",
},
{
    id: "24",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question: "What does Slughorn want to collect from Aragog after he dies?",
    answer_A: "His Heart",
    answer_B: "His Feces",
    answer_C: "His Thorax",
    answer_D: "His Blood",
    correct_answer: "C",
},
{
    id: "25",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question: "Other than Harry, What other young witch/wizard could have been the object of the prophecy regarding Voldemort's downfall?",
    answer_A: "Hermione Granger",
    answer_B: "Ginny Weasley",
    answer_C: "Dean Thomas",
    answer_D: "Neville Longbottom",
    correct_answer: "D",
},
]